<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestMyPsy</string>
    <string name="agression_test">Aggression Test</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="ex_ul">Extremely Unlikely</string>
    <string name="sw_ul">Somewhat Unlikely</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="sw_l">Somewhat Likely</string>
    <string name="ex_l">Extremely Likely</string>
    <string name="take_test">Take Test</string>
    <string name="atq19">Some of my friends think I am a hothead.</string>
    <string name="atq5">If I have to resort to violence to protect my rights, I will.</string>
    <string name="atq29">When people are especially nice to me, I wonder what they want.</string>
    <string name="atq10">I tell my friends openly when I disagree with them.</string>
    <string name="atq9">I have become so mad that I have broken things.</string>
    <string name="atq13">I can’t help getting into arguments when people disagree with me.</string>
    <string name="atq25">I wonder why sometimes I feel so bitter about things.</string>
    <string name="atq1">Once in a while, I can’t control the urge to strike another person.</string>
    <string name="atq18">I am an even-tempered person.</string>
    <string name="atq27">I am suspicious of overly friendly strangers.</string>
    <string name="atq8">I have threatened people I know.</string>
    <string name="atq15">I flare up quickly but get over it quickly.</string>
    <string name="atq2">Given enough provocation, I may hit another person.</string>
    <string name="atq12">When people annoy me, I may tell them what I think of them.</string>
    <string name="atq22">I am sometimes eaten up with jealousy.</string>
    <string name="atq7">I can think of no good reason for ever hitting a person.</string>
    <string name="atq23">At times I feel I have gotten a raw deal out of life.</string>
    <string name="atq21">I have trouble controlling my temper.</string>
    <string name="atq16">When frustrated, I let my irritation show.</string>
    <string name="atq28">I sometimes feel that people are laughing at me behind my back.</string>
    <string name="atq11">I often find myself disagreeing with people.</string>
    <string name="atq3">If somebody hits me, I hit back.</string>
    <string name="atq17">I sometimes feel like a powder keg ready to explode.</string>
    <string name="atq24">Other people always seem to get the breaks.</string>
    <string name="atq6">There are people who pushed me so far that we came to blows.</string>
    <string name="atq26">I know that "friends" talk about me behind my back.</string>
    <string name="atq14">My friends say that I’m somewhat argumentative.</string>
    <string name="atq20">Sometimes I fly off the handle for no good reason.</string>
    <string name="atq4">I get into fights a little more than the average person.</string>
</resources>