<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestMyPsy</string>
    <string name="agression_test">Aggression Test</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="ex_ul">Extremely Unlikely</string>
    <string name="sw_ul">Somewhat Unlikely</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="sw_l">Somewhat Likely</string>
    <string name="ex_l">Extremely Likely</string>
    <string name="take_test">Take Test</string>
    <string name="atq19">Some of my friends think I am a hothead.</string>
    <string name="atq5">If I have to resort to violence to protect my rights, I will.</string>
    <string name="atq29">When people are especially nice to me, I wonder what they want.</string>
    <string name="atq10">I tell my friends openly when I disagree with them.</string>
    <string name="atq9">I have become so mad that I have broken things.</string>
    <string name="atq13">I can\'t help getting into arguments when people disagree with me.</string>
    <string name="atq25">I wonder why sometimes I feel so bitter about things.</string>
    <string name="atq1">Once in a while, I can’t control the urge to strike another person.</string>
    <string name="atq18">I am an even-tempered person.</string>
    <string name="atq27">I am suspicious of overly friendly strangers.</string>
    <string name="atq8">I have threatened people I know.</string>
    <string name="atq15">I flare up quickly but get over it quickly.</string>
    <string name="atq2">Given enough provocation, I may hit another person.</string>
    <string name="atq12">When people annoy me, I may tell them what I think of them.</string>
    <string name="atq22">I am sometimes eaten up with jealousy.</string>
    <string name="atq7">I can think of no good reason for ever hitting a person.</string>
    <string name="atq23">At times I feel I have gotten a raw deal out of life.</string>
    <string name="atq21">I have trouble controlling my temper.</string>
    <string name="atq16">When frustrated, I let my irritation show.</string>
    <string name="atq28">I sometimes feel that people are laughing at me behind my back.</string>
    <string name="atq11">I often find myself disagreeing with people.</string>
    <string name="atq3">If somebody hits me, I hit back.</string>
    <string name="atq17">I sometimes feel like a powder keg ready to explode.</string>
    <string name="atq24">Other people always seem to get the breaks.</string>
    <string name="atq6">There are people who pushed me so far that we came to blows.</string>
    <string name="atq26">I know that "friends" talk about me behind my back.</string>
    <string name="atq14">My friends say that I’m somewhat argumentative.</string>
    <string name="atq20">Sometimes I fly off the handle for no good reason.</string>
    <string name="atq4">I get into fights a little more than the average person.</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="eiq1"> I realise immediately when I lose my temper</string>
    <string name="eiq2">I can \'re-frame\' bad situations quickly </string>
    <string name="eiq3">I am able to always motive myself to do difficult task </string>
    <string name="eiq4">I am always able to see things from the other person\'s viewpoint </string>
    <string name="eiq5">I am an excellent listener </string>
    <string name="eiq6">I know when I am happy </string>
    <string name="eiq7">I do not wear my \'heart on my sleeve\' </string>
    <string name="eiq8">I am usually able to prioritise important activities at work and get on with them</string>
    <string name="eiq9">I am excellent at empathising with someone else\'s problem </string>
    <string name="eiq10">I never interrupt other people\'s conversations </string>
    <string name="eiq11">I usually recognise when I am stressed </string>
    <string name="eiq12">Others can rarely tell what kind of mood I am in </string>
    <string name="eiq13">I always meet deadlines </string>
    <string name="eiq14">I can tell if someone is not happy with me </string>
    <string name="eiq15">I am good at adapting and mixing with a variety of people </string>
    <string name="eiq16">When I am being \'emotional\' I am aware of this </string>
    <string name="eiq17">I rarely \'fly off the handle\' at other people  </string>
    <string name="eiq18"> I never waste time </string>
    <string name="eiq19">I can tell if a team of people are not getting along with each other </string>
    <string name="eiq20">When I feel anxious I usually can account for the reason(s) </string>
    <string name="eiq21">Difficult people do not annoy me </string>
    <string name="eiq22">I do not prevaricate </string>
    <string name="eiq23">I can usually understand why people are being difficult towards me </string>
    <string name="eiq24"> I love to meet new people and get to know what makes them \'tick\'</string>
    <string name="eiq25">I always know when I\'m being unreasonable</string>
    <string name="eiq26">I can consciously alter my frame of mind or mood </string>
    <string name="eiq27">I believe you should do the difficult things first </string>
    <string name="eiq28">Other individuals are not \'difficult\' just \'different\' </string>
    <string name="eiq29">I need a variety of work colleagues to make my job interesting </string>
    <string name="eiq30">Awareness of my own emotions is very important to me at all times </string>
    <string name="eiq31">I do not let stressful situations or people affect me once I have left work </string>
    <string name="eiq32">Delayed gratification is a virtue that I hold to </string>
    <string name="eiq33">I can understand if I am being unreasonable </string>
    <string name="eiq34">I like to ask questions to find out what it is important to people </string>
    <string name="eiq35">I can tell if someone has upset or annoyed me </string>
    <string name="eiq36">I rarely worry about work or life in general </string>
    <string name="eiq37">I believe in \'Action this Day\' </string>
    <string name="eiq38">I can understand why my actions sometimes offend others </string>
    <string name="eiq39">I see working with difficult people as simply a challenge to win them over </string>
    <string name="eiq40">I can let anger \'go\' quickly so that it no longer affects me  </string>
    <string name="eiq41">I can suppress my emotions when I need to </string>
    <string name="eiq42">People are the most interesting thing in life for me </string>
    <string name="eiq43">I can always motivate myself even when I feel low </string>
    <string name="eiq44">I can sometimes see things from others\' point of view </string>
    <string name="eiq45">I am good at reconciling differences with other people </string>
    <string name="eiq46">I know what makes me happy </string>
    <string name="eiq47">Others often do not know how I am feeling about things </string>
    <string name="eiq48">Motivations has been the key to my success </string>
    <string name="eiq49">Reasons for disagreements are always clear to me </string>
    <string name="eiq50">I generally build solid relationships with those I work with </string>
    <string name="eiTest">Emotional Intelligence Test</string>
    <string name="qolTest">Quality of Life Test</string>
    <string name="qol1">How would you rate your quality of life?</string>
    <string name="qol2">How satisfied are you with your health?</string>
    <string name="qol3">To what extent do you feel that physical pain prevents you from doing what you need to do?</string>
    <string name="qol4">How much do you need any medical treatment to function in your life?</string>
    <string name="qol5">How much do you enjoy life?</string>
    <string name="qol6">To what extent do you feel your life to be meaningful?</string>
    <string name="qol7">How well are you able to concentrate?</string>
    <string name="qol8">How safe do you feel in your daily life?</string>
    <string name="qol9">How healthy is your physical environment?</string>
    <string name="qol10">. Do you have enough energy for everyday life?</string>
    <string name="qol11">Are you able to accept your bodily appearance?</string>
    <string name="qol12">Have you enough money to meet your needs?</string>
    <string name="qol13">How available to you is the information that you need in your day-to-day life?</string>
    <string name="qol14">To what extent do you have the opportunity for leisure activities?</string>
    <string name="qol15">How well are you able to get around?</string>
    <string name="qol16">How satisfied are you with your sleep?</string>
    <string name="qol17">How satisfied are you with your ability to perform your daily living activities.</string>
    <string name="qol18">How satisfied are you with your capacity for work?</string>
    <string name="qol19">How satisfied are you with yourself?</string>
    <string name="qol20">How satisfied are you with your personal relationships?</string>
    <string name="qol21"> How satisfied are you with your sex life?</string>
    <string name="qol22">How satisfied are you with the support you get fromyour friends?</string>
    <string name="qol23">How satisfied are you with the conditions of your living place?</string>
    <string name="qol24">How satisfied are you with your access to health services?</string>
    <string name="qol25"> How satisfied are you with your mode of transportation?</string>
    <string name="qol26">How often do you have negative feelings, such as blue mood, despair, anxiety, depression?</string>

    <string name="very_poor">Very Poor</string>
    <string name="poor">Poor</string>
    <string name="neither_nor_poor">Neither poor nor good</string>
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="very_good">Very Good</string>
    <string name="not_at_all">Not at All</string>
    <string name="a_little">A Little</string>
    <string name="a_moderate_amount">A Moderate Amount</string>
    <string name="moderately">Moderately</string>
    <string name="mostly">Mostly</string>
    <string name="completely">Completely</string>
    <string name="very_much">Very Much</string>
    <string name="extreme_amount">An Extreme Amount</string>
    <string name="extremely">Extremely</string>
    <string name="very_dissatisfied">Very Dissatisfied</string>
    <string name="dissatisfied">Dissatisfied</string>
    <string name="neither_nor_dissatisfied">Neither Satisfied Nor Dissatisfied</string>
    <string name="satisfied">Satisfied</string>
    <string name="never">Never</string>
    <string name="seldom">Seldom</string>
    <string name="very_often">Very Often</string>

    <string name="neither_nor_well">Neither Poor Nor Well</string>
    <string name="well">Well</string>
    <string name="very_well">Very Well</string>

    <string name="quite_often">Quite Often</string>
    <string name="always">Always</string>
    <string name="very_satisfied">Very Satisfied</string>

    <string name="ptTest">Personality Test</string>
    <string name="ptq1">1. I Am the life of the party.</string>
    <string name="ptq2">2. I Feel little concern for others.</string>
    <string name="ptq3">3. I Am always prepared.</string>
    <string name="ptq4">4. I Get stressed out easily.</string>
    <string name="ptq5">5. I Have a rich vocabulary.</string>
    <string name="ptq6">6. I Don\'t talk a lot.</string>
    <string name="ptq7">7. I Am interested in people.</string>
    <string name="ptq8">8. I Leave my belongings around.</string>
    <string name="ptq9">9. I Am relaxed most of the time</string>
    <string name="ptq10">10. I Have difficulty understanding abstract ideas.</string>
    <string name="ptq11">11. I Feel comfortable around people. </string>
    <string name="ptq12">12. I Insult people.</string>
    <string name="ptq13">13. I Pay attention to details.</string>
    <string name="ptq14">14. I Worry about things.</string>
    <string name="ptq15">15. I Have a vivid imagination.</string>
    <string name="ptq16">16. I Keep in the background.</string>
    <string name="ptq17">17. I Sympathize with others\' feelings.</string>
    <string name="ptq18">18. I Make a mess of things.</string>
    <string name="ptq19">19. I Seldom feel blue.</string>
    <string name="ptq20">20. I Am not interested in abstract ideas</string>

    <string name="ptq21">21. I Start conversations.</string>
    <string name="ptq22">22. I Am not interested in other people\'s problems.</string>
    <string name="ptq23">23. I Get chores done right away.</string>
    <string name="ptq24">24. I Am easily disturbed. </string>
    <string name="ptq25">25. I Have excellent ideas.</string>
    <string name="ptq26">26. I Have little to say.</string>
    <string name="ptq27">27. I Have a soft heart</string>
    <string name="ptq28">28. I Often forget to put things back in their proper place.</string>
    <string name="ptq29">29. I Get upset easily.</string>


    <string name="ptq30">30. I Do not have a good imagination</string>
    <string name="ptq31">31. I Talk to a lot of different people at parties.</string>
    <string name="ptq32">32. I Am not really interested in others.</string>
    <string name="ptq33">33. I Like order.</string>
    <string name="ptq34">34. I Change my mood a lot.</string>
    <string name="ptq35">35. I Am quick to understand things.</string>
    <string name="ptq36">36. I Don\'t like to draw attention to myself.</string>
    <string name="ptq37">37. I Take time out for others.</string>
    <string name="ptq38">38. I Shirk my duties</string>
    <string name="ptq39">39. I Have frequent mood swings.</string>


    <string name="ptq40">40. I Use difficult words.</string>
    <string name="ptq41">41. I Don\'t mind being the center of attention.</string>
    <string name="ptq42">42. I Feel others emotions</string>
    <string name="ptq43">43. I Follow a schedule</string>
    <string name="ptq44">44. I Get irritated easily</string>
    <string name="ptq45">45. I Spend time reflecting on things</string>
    <string name="ptq46">46. I Am quiet around strangers</string>
    <string name="ptq47">47. I Make people feel at ease.</string>
    <string name="ptq48">48. I Am exacting in my work</string>
    <string name="ptq49">49. I Often feel blue.</string>

    <string name="ptq50">50. I Am full of ideas.</string>

    <string name="saTest">SelfActualization Test</string>

    <string name="sa1">1. I understand that taking some risk to realize one\'s potential is always better. </string>
    <string name="sa2">2. I make all possible efforts to achieve my goal. </string>
    <string name="sa3">3. It is better to maintain your individuality than to be like others. </string>
    <string name="sa4">4. People love me because I love others too</string>
    <string name="sa5">5. I am bothered by the fear of being inadequate in my work</string>
    <string name="sa6">6. In context of new ideas and experiences I am always ready to change my opinion and values. </string>
    <string name="sa7">7. I have little interest in solving complex problems or making it easy. </string>
    <string name="sa8">8. I have no mission in life to which I feel dedicated. </string>
    <string name="sa9">9. I do not feel ashamed of any of my emotions. </string>
    <string name="sa10">10. I feel that I have right to be angry at those I love.</string>
    <string name="sa11">11. I am honest to myself as well as to others</string>
    <string name="sa12">12. I do not take the responsibility of helping anybody</string>
    <string name="sa13">13. I believe that people are essentially good and they can be trusted upon. </string>
    <string name="sa14">14. 1 do not accept my weaknesses</string>
    <string name="sa15">15. I feel essential to evaluate my merits and demerits. </string>
    <string name="sa16">16. 1 do not feel hesitation in expressing my feeling knowing fully well that its consequence will not be good</string>
    <string name="sa17">17. It is a difficult task for me to achieve something in accordance with my potential.</string>
    <string name="sa18">18. I have a clear vision of my needs, opinion and values.</string>
    <string name="sa19">19. For me satisfaction of my physical needs is more essential than constructiveness and creativity. </string>
    <string name="sa20">20. I am afraid of failure. </string>
    <string name="sa21">21. I am fully conscious of my potentialities</string>
    <string name="sa22">22. I can like even those with whom I have disagreement. </string>

    <string name="spiTest">Social Phobia Test</string>
    <string name="spt1">1. I am afraid of people in authority.</string>
    <string name="spt2">2. I am bothered by blushing in front of people. </string>
    <string name="spt3">3. Parties and social events scare me. </string>
    <string name="spt4">4. I avoid talking to people I don’t know. </string>
    <string name="spt5">5. Being criticized scares me a lot. </string>
    <string name="spt6">6. I avoid doing things or speaking to people for fear of embarrassment. </string>
    <string name="spt7">7. Sweating in front of people causes me distress. </string>
    <string name="spt8">8. I avoid going to parties. </string>
    <string name="spt9">9. I avoid activities in which I am the center of attention </string>
    <string name="spt10">10. Talking to strangers scares me. </string>
    <string name="spt11">11. I avoid having to give speeches </string>
    <string name="spt12">12. I would do anything to avoid being criticized. </string>
    <string name="spt13">13. Heart palpitations bother me when I am around people. </string>
    <string name="spt14">14. I am afraid of doing things when people might be watching. </string>
    <string name="spt15">15. Being embarrassed or looking stupid are among my worst fears. </string>
    <string name="spt16">16. I avoid speaking to anyone in authority. </string>
    <string name="spt17">17. Trembling or shaking in front of others is distressing to me. </string>
    <string name="eq1">1. I can easily tell if someone else wants to enter a conversation.</string>
    <string name="eq2">2. I prefer animals to humans.</string>
    <string name="eq3">3. I try to keep up with the current trends and fashions.</string>
    <string name="eq4">4. I find it difficult to explain to others things that I understand easily, when they don\'t understand it the first time.</string>
    <string name="eq5">5. I dream most nights.</string>
    <string name="eq6">6. I really enjoy caring for other people.</string>
    <string name="eq7">7. I try to solve my own problems rather than discussing them with others.</string>
    <string name="eq8">8. I find it hard to know what to do in a social situation.</string>
    <string name="eq9">9. I am at my best first thing in the morning.</string>
    <string name="eq10">10. People often tell me that I went too far in driving my point home in a discussion.</string>
    <string name="eq11">11. It doesn\'t bother me too much if I am late meeting a friend.</string>
    <string name="eq12">12. Friendships and relationships are just too difficult, so I tend not to bother with them.</string>
    <string name="eq13">13. I would never break a law, no matter how minor.</string>
    <string name="eq14">14. I often find it difficult to judge if something is rude or polite.</string>
    <string name="eq15">15. In a conversation, I tend to focus on my own thoughts rather than on what my listener might be thinking.</string>
    <string name="eq16">16. I prefer practical jokes to verbal humor.</string>
    <string name="eq17">17. I live life for today rather than the future.</string>
    <string name="eq18">18. When I was a child, I enjoyed cutting up worms to see what would happen.</string>
    <string name="eq19">19. I can pick up quickly if someone says one thing but means another.</string>
    <string name="eq20">20. I tend to have very strong opinions about morality.</string>
    <string name="eq21">21. It is hard for me to see why some things upset people so much.</string>
    <string name="eq22">22. I find it easy to put myself in somebody else\'s shoes.</string>
    <string name="eq23">23. I think that good manners are the most important thing a parent can teach their child.</string>
    <string name="eq24">24. I like to do things on the spur of the moment.</string>
    <string name="eq25">25. I am good at predicting how someone will feel.</string>
    <string name="eq26">26. I am quick to spot when someone in a group is feeling awkward or uncomfortable.</string>
    <string name="eq27">27. If I say something that someone else is offended by, I think that that\'s their problem, not mine.</string>
    <string name="eq28">28. If anyone asked me if I liked their haircut, I would reply truthfully, even if I didn\'t like it.</string>
    <string name="eq29">29. I can\'t always see why someone should have felt offended by a remark.</string>
    <string name="eq30">30. People often tell me that I am very unpredictable.</string>
    <string name="eq31">31. I enjoy being the center of attention at any social gathering.</string>
    <string name="eq32">32. Seeing people cry doesn\'t really upset me.</string>
    <string name="eq33">33. I enjoy having discussions about politics.</string>
    <string name="eq34">34. I am very blunt, which some people take to be rudeness, even though this is unintentional.</string>
    <string name="eq35">35. I don\'t find social situations confusing.</string>
    <string name="eq36">36. Other people tell me I am good at understanding how they are feeling and what they are thinking.</string>
    <string name="eq37">37. When I talk to people, I tend to talk about their experiences rather than my own.</string>
    <string name="eq38">38. It upsets me to see an animal in pain.</string>
    <string name="eq39">39. I am able to make decisions without being influenced by people\'s feelings.</string>
    <string name="eq40">40. I can\'t relax until I have done everything I had planned to do that day.</string>
    <string name="eq41">41. I can easily tell if someone else is interested or bored with what I am saying.</string>
    <string name="eq42">42. I get upset if I see people suffering on news programs.</string>
    <string name="eq43">43. Friends usually talk to me about their problems as they say that I am very understanding.</string>
    <string name="eq44">44. I can sense if I am intruding, even if the other person doesn\'t tell me.</string>
    <string name="eq45">45. I often start new hobbies, but quickly become bored with them and move on to something else.</string>
    <string name="eq46">46. People sometimes tell me that I have gone too far with teasing.</string>
    <string name="eq47">47. I would be too nervous to go on a big rollercoaster.</string>
    <string name="eq48">48. Other people often say that I am insensitive, though I don\'t always see why.</string>
    <string name="eq49">49. If I see a stranger in a group, I think that it is up to them to make an effort to join in.</string>
    <string name="eq50">50. I usually stay emotionally detached when watching a film.</string>
    <string name="eq51">51. I like to be very organized in day-to-day life and often makes lists of the chores I have to do.</string>
    <string name="eq52">52. I can tune into how someone else feels rapidly and intuitively.</string>
    <string name="eq53">53. I don\'t like to take risks.</string>
    <string name="eq54">54. I can easily work out what another person might want to talk about.</string>
    <string name="eq55">55. I can tell if someone is masking their true emotion.</string>
    <string name="eq56">56. Before making a decision, I always weigh up the pros and cons.</string>
    <string name="eq57">57. I don\'t consciously work out the rules of social situations.</string>
    <string name="eq58">58. I am good at predicting what someone will do.</string>
    <string name="eq59">59. I tend to get emotionally involved with a friend\'s problems.</string>
    <string name="eq60">60. I can usually appreciate the other person\'s viewpoint, even if I don\'t agree with it.</string>
    <string name="ocd1">1. I have saved up so many things that they get in the way.</string>
    <string name="ocd2">2. I check things more often than necessary.</string>
    <string name="ocd3">3. I get upset if objects are not arranged properly.</string>
    <string name="ocd4">4. I feel compelled to count while I am doing things.</string>
    <string name="ocd5">5. I find it difficult to touch an object when I know it has been touched by strangers or certain people.</string>
    <string name="ocd6">6. I find it difficult to control my own thoughts.</string>
    <string name="ocd7">7. I collect things I don\'t need.</string>
    <string name="ocd8">8. I repeatedly check doors, windows, drawers, etc.</string>
    <string name="ocd9">9. I get upset if others change the way I have arranged things.</string>
    <string name="ocd10">10. I feel I have to repeat certain numbers.</string>
    <string name="ocd11">11. I sometimes have to wash or clean myself simply because I feel contaminated.</string>
    <string name="ocd12">12. I am upset by unpleasant thoughts that come into my mind against my will.</string>
    <string name="ocd13">13. I avoid throwing things away because I am afraid I might need them later.</string>
    <string name="ocd14">14. I repeatedly check gas and water taps and light switches after turning them off.</string>
    <string name="ocd15">15. I need things to be arranged in a particular way.</string>
    <string name="ocd16">16. I feel that there are good and bad numbers.</string>
    <string name="ocd17">17. I wash my hands more often and longer than necessary.</string>
    <string name="ocd18">18. I frequently get nasty thoughts and have difficulty in getting rid of them.</string>
    <string name="ia1">1. I find myself using my smartphone or computer longer than I planned to.</string>
    <string name="ia2">2. I would rather be on my smartphone or computer than interact with my partner.</string>
    <string name="ia3">3. I would rather spend time online than do things around the house.</string>
    <string name="ia4">4. My performance in school or at work suffers because of the amount of time I spend online.</string>
    <string name="ia5">5. People close to me are concerned about the amount of time I spend on my smartphone or computer.</string>
    <string name="ia6">6. When asked what I do online, I prefer not to answer.</string>
    <string name="ia7">7. My productivity and attentiveness suffers because of the amount of time I spend online.</string>
    <string name="ia8">8. I check my social media, text messages, or emails first thing after waking up.</string>
    <string name="ia9">9. I am bothered when people interrupt me while I am using my computer or smartphone.</string>
    <string name="ia10">10. I feel anxious when I do not have my smartphone with me.</string>
    <string name="ia11">11. I use the internet to escape from my real life.</string>
    <string name="ia12">12. I would be less interesting and happy without access to the internet.</string>
    <string name="ia13">13. I put off things I have to do by using my computer or smartphone.</string>
    <string name="ia14">14. When I am unable to use my smartphone, I miss it or think about what I could be doing online.</string>
    <string name="ia15">15. I stay up later at night than I had intended due to doing things online.</string>
    <string name="ia16">16. I would rather stay home and use the internet than go out with friends.</string>
    <string name="ia17">17. I have tried to reduce my smartphone or internet use without success.</string>
    <string name="ia18">18. I am concerned about missing out on thing online when not checking my smartphone.</string>
    <string name="ocd_test">OCD Test</string>
    <string name="eq_test">Empathy Quotient Test</string>
    <string name="ia_test">Internet addiction Test</string>


</resources>