<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestMyPsy</string>
    <string name="agression_test">Aggression Test</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="ex_ul">Extremely Unlikely</string>
    <string name="sw_ul">Somewhat Unlikely</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="sw_l">Somewhat Likely</string>
    <string name="ex_l">Extremely Likely</string>
    <string name="take_test">Take Test</string>
    <string name="atq19">Some of my friends think I am a hothead.</string>
    <string name="atq5">If I have to resort to violence to protect my rights, I will.</string>
    <string name="atq29">When people are especially nice to me, I wonder what they want.</string>
    <string name="atq10">I tell my friends openly when I disagree with them.</string>
    <string name="atq9">I have become so mad that I have broken things.</string>
    <string name="atq13">I can’t help getting into arguments when people disagree with me.</string>
    <string name="atq25">I wonder why sometimes I feel so bitter about things.</string>
    <string name="atq1">Once in a while, I can’t control the urge to strike another person.</string>
    <string name="atq18">I am an even-tempered person.</string>
    <string name="atq27">I am suspicious of overly friendly strangers.</string>
    <string name="atq8">I have threatened people I know.</string>
    <string name="atq15">I flare up quickly but get over it quickly.</string>
    <string name="atq2">Given enough provocation, I may hit another person.</string>
    <string name="atq12">When people annoy me, I may tell them what I think of them.</string>
    <string name="atq22">I am sometimes eaten up with jealousy.</string>
    <string name="atq7">I can think of no good reason for ever hitting a person.</string>
    <string name="atq23">At times I feel I have gotten a raw deal out of life.</string>
    <string name="atq21">I have trouble controlling my temper.</string>
    <string name="atq16">When frustrated, I let my irritation show.</string>
    <string name="atq28">I sometimes feel that people are laughing at me behind my back.</string>
    <string name="atq11">I often find myself disagreeing with people.</string>
    <string name="atq3">If somebody hits me, I hit back.</string>
    <string name="atq17">I sometimes feel like a powder keg ready to explode.</string>
    <string name="atq24">Other people always seem to get the breaks.</string>
    <string name="atq6">There are people who pushed me so far that we came to blows.</string>
    <string name="atq26">I know that "friends" talk about me behind my back.</string>
    <string name="atq14">My friends say that I’m somewhat argumentative.</string>
    <string name="atq20">Sometimes I fly off the handle for no good reason.</string>
    <string name="atq4">I get into fights a little more than the average person.</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name = "eiq1"> I realise immediately when I lose my temper</string>
    <string name = "eiq2">I can 'reframe' bad situations quickly </string>
    <string name = "eiq3">I am able to always motive myself to do difficult task </string>
    <string name = "eiq4">I am always able to see things from the other person's viewpoint </string>
    <string name = "eiq5">I am an excellent listener </string>
    <string name = "eiq6">I know when I am happy </string>
    <string name = "eiq7">I do not wear my 'heart on my sleeve' </string>
    <string name = "eiq8">I am usually able to prioritise important activities at work and get on with them</string>
    <string name = "eiq9">I am excellent at empathising with someone else's problem </string>
    <string name = "eiq10">I never interrupt other people's conversations </string>
    <string name = "eiq11">I usually recognise when I am stressed </string>
    <string name = "eiq12">Others can rarely tell what kind of mood I am in </string>
    <string name = "eiq13">I always meet deadlines </string>
    <string name = "eiq14">I can tell if someone is not happy with me </string>
    <string name = "eiq15">I am good at adapting and mixing with a variety of people </string>
    <string name = "eiq16">When I am being 'emotional' I am aware of this </string>
    <string name = "eiq17">I rarely 'fly off the handle' at other people  </string>
    <string name = "eiq18"> I never waste time </string>
    <string name = "eiq19">I can tell if a team of people are not getting along with each other </string>
    <string name = "eiq20">When I feel anxious I usually can account for the reason(s) </string>
    <string name = "eiq21">Difficult people do not annoy me </string>
    <string name = "eiq22">I do not prevaricat </string>
    <string name = "eiq23">I can usually understand why people are being difficult towards me </string>
    <string name = "eiq24"> I love to meet new people and get to know what makes them 'tick'</string>
    <string name = "eiq25">I always know when I'm being unreasonable</string>
    <string name = "eiq26">I can consciously alter my frame of mind or mood </string>
    <string name = "eiq27">I believe you should do the difficult things first </string>
    <string name = "eiq28">Other individuals are not 'difficult' just 'different' </string>
    <string name = "eiq29">I need a variety of work colleagues to make my job interesting </string>
    <string name = "eiq30">Awareness of my own emotions is very important to me at all times </string>
    <string name = "eiq31">I do not let stressful situations or people affect me once I have left work </string>
    <string name = "eiq32">Delayed gratification is a virtue that I hold to </string>
    <string name = "eiq33">I can understand if I am being unreasonable </string>
    <string name = "eiq34">I like to ask questions to find out what it is important to people </string>
    <string name = "eiq35">I can tell if someone has upset or annoyed me </string>
    <string name = "eiq36">I rarely worry about work or life in general </string>
    <string name = "eiq37">I believe in 'Action this Day' </string>
    <string name = "eiq38">I can understand why my actions sometimes offend others </string>
    <string name = "eiq39">I see working with difficult people as simply a challenge to win them over </string>
    <string name = "eiq40">I can let anger 'go' quickly so that it no longer affects me  </string>
    <string name = "eiq41">I can suppress my emotions when I need to </string>
    <string name = "eiq42">People are the most interesting thing in life for me </string>
    <string name = "eiq43">I can always motivate myself even when I feel low </string>
    <string name = "eiq44">I can sometimes see things from others' point of view </string>
    <string name = "eiq45">I am good at reconciling differences with other people </string>
    <string name = "eiq46">I know what makes me happy </string>
    <string name = "eiq47">Others often do not know how I am feeling about things </string>
    <string name = "eiq48">Motivations has been the key to my success </string>
    <string name = "eiq49">Reasons for disagreements are always clear to me </string>
    <string name = "eiq50">I generally build solid relationships with those I work with </string>
    <string name = "ei_test">Emotional Intelligence Test</string>
</resources>